- 嘿，伙计们… - 等等，我来跟他们讲。
- Hey,guys.. - Wait! Let me tell them.
-好 -乔伊要
- Sure. - Joey's gonna be..
在一个益智节目中做嘉宾了。
a celebrity guest on a game show.
真的？哪个节目？
Really? Which one?
鱼，海草
Fish. Seaweed.
- 沉船… -海中之物…
- A sunken ship. - Things you find in the ocean.
-你要上智力金字塔! - 对
- You're gonna be on Pyramid! - Yeah.
-哦，那是我们最喜欢的益智节目了! - 除了匹配赛以外!
- That was our favorite game show ever. - Except for Match Game.
还有输赢签。
Or Win,Lose or Draw.
瞧瞧我结的亲家。
What did I marry into?
你们想明天来看我录节目吗？
You guys wanna come and watch me tape the show?
不行，我们要给菲比开个婚前告别单身狂欢。
Oh,we can't. We're throwing Phoebe a bachelorette party.
对喽，抱歉，兄弟们，此路不通。
Yeah. Sorry,boys,this ride's closing.
哦，钱德和我要参加一个校友聚会。
And Chandler and I have this stupid college alumni thing.
难以置信你要跟多尼・奥斯蒙德做节目。
I can't believe you get to meet Donny Osmond.
当真？
Seriously?
罗斯和我以前总想变成多尼和马瑞
Ross and I always wanted to be Donny and Marie.
你们俩还越说越起劲儿了。
You guys just keep getting cooler and cooler.
对，我们以前还在家里和朋友面前表演过
Yeah,we used to perform for our family and friends.
哦，没错，我还真给它忘了。
Oh,God,that's right. I blocked that out.
我要离开你了
I'm leaving you.
脱衣舞男之泪
The.One.Where.The.Stripper.Cries
又见到这些人了。
It's so weird to see all these people again.
哦，我的上帝，那是杰佛.克拉瑞。
Oh,my God,look. There's Jeffrey Klarik.
-谁? -约翰.卢瑟夫的室友。
- Who? - He was roommates with John Rosoff.
他当时跟安卓.特布里诺拍拖。
He went out with Andrea Tamborino.
她后来又跟麦克.斯克劳夫好上了。
She dumped him for Michael Skloff.
我上的是这所学校吗？
Did I go to this school?
嘿，那是米西.戈尔伯格，你肯定记得她。
Hey,there's Missy Goldberg. You gotta remember her.
当然，她很正点。
Sure. Nice.
伙计儿，你可跟我妹妹结了婚的。
Dude,you're married to my sister.
你说的没错，我夸她正点就是跟她不正经了？
You're right. By saying "nice," I'm virtually licking her.
嘿，我听说她又单身了 你说我是不是该跟她约会呢？
Hey,I hear she's single again. You think I should ask her out?
你是不是想要打破君子协定？
Are you asking permission to break the pact?
对了，求求你。
Yes,please.
瞧瞧乐队的传单。
Hey. Hey,check out the fliers for the band.
-我在机房的苹果机上做的。 -乖乖
- I made them on a Macintosh. - Awesome.
名字还挺醒目的。
The name really stands out.
感谢24号大小的 海维提卡粗体字（苹果电脑默认字体）
Thanks to a little something called Helvetica Bold 24-point.
伙计儿，我们要在亚洲学生联盟摇滚了。
Man,we're gonna rock that Asian Student Union.
- 嘿，伙计们。 - 嘿，米西。
- Hey,guys. - Hey,Missy.
-你知道吗，我们乐队星期五演出。 -是啊，你该来看看。
- Our band is playing on Friday. - Yeah,you should come check us out.
我们管它叫"行，还是不行"。
We're called Way/No Way.
- 不行。 - 行!
- No way. - Way.
- 好吧，到时见 - 新鲜
- Great. I'll be there. - Fresh.
- 老板. - 薄荷.
- Boss. - Mint.
- 她走了。 - 我知道。
- She's gone. - I know it.
-你知道吗，我一定要约到她。 -伙计儿，我还想约她呢。
- I am totally gonna ask her out. - Dude,I was gonna ask her out.
-是我先说的，兄弟。 -那我还先想到的呢，老哥。
- I said it first,bro. - Well,I thought it first,Homes.
-听着，你要是约… -等等，我们在干吗呢？
- Look,if you date.. - Wait! Wait! What are we doing?
我们不需要为了某些女孩而反目成仇
What we have is too important to mess it up over some girl.
我的意思是，我们随时都能得到我们想要的女人
I mean,we can get laid any time we want.
就是。
Totally.
-我高中就有性生活了。 -我也是，我是情场高手。
- I had sex in high school. - Me too. I'm good at it.
好吧，我们俩立个君子协定，
All right,I say we make a pact.
谁都不许跟米西.戈尔伯格约会。
Neither of us will go out with Missy Goldberg.
一言为定。
You got it.
那么，现在我们就不能跟米西.戈尔伯格 菲比.凯特
That's Missy Goldberg,Phoebe Cates and Molly Ringwald..
-还有莫莉.里沃特约会了 -没错，打包。
- who we can't go out with. - Those are the pacts.
哦，还有西娜.伊斯特 反正我们也追不上她。
And Sheena Easton. But we probably couldn't get her anyway.
你追不上她倒是真的。
Maybe not you.
好吧，我正式授权允许你打破君子协定。
Well,I officially give you permission to break the pact.
谢谢。
Thank you.
好，我要上啦。 嘿，还记得上学时你跟女孩说话都慌神吗？
Here I go. Hey,remember how scary it used to be going up to girls in college?
- 你的手在发抖呢。 - 我知道，我还一个劲地冒汗。
- Your hands are shaking. - I know. And I can't stop sweating.
5，4，3，鼓掌。
Five,four,three. Applause.
哦!
Yeah!
欢迎大家，这里是智力金字塔，肥皂剧之周。
Welcome. It is Soap Opera Week here on Pyramid.
来看看选手们 首先，是数据库专家金.拉斯特。
Let's meet our contestants. First,Gene Lester is a database specialist.
他的搭档是“我们的日子” 剧中的明星 乔伊崔比亚尼。
He's gonna be playing with Days of Our Lives star Joey Tribbiani.
嘿，我知道普通人跟名人在一起时都会紧张。
I know it can be intimidating for regular people to be around celebrities..
不过没事儿，我跟你差不多 就是好看点儿，钱多点儿。
but relax. I'm just like you,only better-looking and richer.
…要跟"综合医院" 剧中的明星莱丝莉.查尔森搭档。
She'll be playing with star of General Hospital,Leslie Charleson.
欢迎大家，祝各位好运。 我们开始玩智力金字塔，好吗？
Welcome,everybody. Good luck to all of you. Let's play Pyramid.
我们在节目开始之前已经抛过硬币了。
All right? Now,we flipped a coin before the show.
金，你猜对硬币，所以你先开始。
Gene,you won the toss,so you'll start. Which category?
- 你选哪组题目？ - 我选"你越过了那条线"。
- "You Crossed the Line." - "You Crossed the Line." Joey..
乔伊，你给金描述那些有线条的东西。
describe for Gene these things that have lines.
限时20秒。 预备，开始。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock,please. Ready? Go.
（超市）呃，象超市一样的商店…哦！
Okay,it's a store like a supermarket.
（笔记本）我明白，我明白。 呃，我写…
I see what I did there. Okay,okay. I'm writing in my..
-日记。 -不是，更象个笔记本…该死！
- Diary. - No,more like a notebook.
（设计图）哦，要是我建所房子
If I'm building a house,the plan..
那个规划，不是叫平面图的…
isn't called a "shmooprint"..
这样都不行？
I can't do that either?
（足球场）在高中，有一次我跟个女孩做爱在…
In high school,I once had sex with a girl right in the middle of the..?
-食堂。 -是有过那么一次，但那不是他们要的那个词
- Cafeteria? - Yeah,but they're not looking for that.
-你们办的还真不错。 -哦，你喜欢吗？
- Thank you so much for this. - You like it?
哦，我的上帝，还挺高雅的呢。
Oh,my God,it's all so elegant.
什么时候开始来点儿刺激的？
When's the dirty stuff starting?
-什么？ -你知道的，脱衣舞男啦
- What? - The strippers and the guys dancing..
男子艳舞啦，屁屁晃来晃去之类的。
and,you know,pee-pees flying about.
菲比，我… 今天没有艳舞表演。
Phoebe,I.. There isn't gonna be any "flying about."
事实上，我们觉得我们老大不小的了 还玩这些？
We thought we were a little too mature for stuff like that.
哦，好吧。
Oh,okay.
我知道你们在干吗，好的。 今天就是个茶话会，好的。
I see what you're doing. That's fine. This is all there is. Just tea. Okay.
好淫荡
Raunchy.
真的，菲比，这不是那种狂欢。
Seriously,Phoebe,it's not gonna be that kind of a party.
真的？这就是
Really? So this is..?
我的婚前单身告别会？
This is my big sendoff into married life?
瑞秋，我可就只有这一次单身告别会啊。
Rachel,this is the only bachelorette party I'm ever gonna have.
我提包里可有一大筐东西呢。
I've got a big wad of ones in my purse.
真的？今天就只是茶话会？
Really? I mean,really? It's just tea?
当然不是了。
No.
-菲比，还有别的呢。 -好吧
- Phoebe,of course there's more. - Okay.
我是说，我去问问莫妮卡
I mean,let me just go talk to Monica..
看什么时候上屁屁艳舞。
and get an ETA on the pee-pees.
我们有点问题
We've got a problem.
哦,天啊! 有谁发现我的创可贴在她们的烤饼里了吗?
Oh,my God. Did someone find my Band-Aid in their scone?
那不是一个杏仁吗?
That wasn't an apricot?
-什么问题? -菲比想要脱衣舞男
- What's the problem? - Okay. Phoebe wants a stripper.
我记得我说过 我们长大了,不需要那个了
I thought we said we were too grown up for that.
对,但是她想要的
Yeah,well,it's what she wants.
嘿,为什么有脱衣舞男电话的一页折上了?
Hey,why is the page that has strippers on it dog-eared?
钱德在土尔沙时，我太无聊了
Chandler was in Tulsa. I was bored.
请别告诉他
Please don't tell him.
现在,金,我要提醒你 必须答对全部6题才能留下来
Now,Gene,I must remind you,you need all six of these to stay in the game.
给乔伊描述冰箱里的物品。
Describe for Joey "things you find in your refrigerator."
我看这简直是给我们送分啊。
They might as well just give us the points.
限时20秒。预备，开始。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock. Ready? Go.
（奶油）-你往咖啡里加的东西。 -勺子，手，脸。
- You put this in your coffee. - A spoon. Your hands. Your face.
- 它是白色的。 - 纸，雪，鬼！
- It's white. - Paper. Snow. A ghost!
-它比牛奶重。 -呃，石头，狗，地球。
- It's heavier than milk. - A rock. A dog. The Earth.
过。
Pass.
（蛋黄酱）-你往三明治上放的东西。 -萨拉米香肠，凤尾鱼，果酱。
- You put it on a sandwich. - Salami. Anchovies. Jam.
- 白色的。 - 纸，雪，鬼！
- It's white. - Paper. Snow. A ghost!
- 它使用鸡蛋做的。 - 小鸡？
- It's made from eggs. - Chickens?
过
Pass.
（番茄酱）- 你往汉堡包上放的东西。 - 番茄酱。调味品
- You put this on a hamburger. - Ketchup! Relish!
停。
Stop!
哦，时间到。 乔伊，你…
Oh,time's up. Well,Joey,you were..
超常发挥了。金..
almost on a roll there. Gene..
你下半场还可能有机会进入决胜圈的。 但是现在
you'll have a chance to go to the Winner's Circle,but now..
亨瑞达 你待会儿将进入决胜圈一试运气赢取10000美元。
Henrietta,you're going to the Winner's Circle to try your luck for $10,000..
不要走开。
right after this. Don't go away.
现在进广告
And we're out.
-刚才的番茄酱怎么样啊? -对!印象深刻
- How about that ketchup thing,huh? - Yeah. Impressive.
哦，我们没赢，不过乐在其中也不错，对吧？
Oh,so we didn't win. But it's fun to play the game,right?
我有个孩子刚上大学，我的膝盖要做手术
I got a kid starting college. I have to get surgery on my knee.
你刚刚让我损失一万美金。
You just lost me 10 grand.
喔。
Oh,wow.
抱歉，我保证下一轮我们发挥好一点。
I'm so sorry. Okay,I promise,we'll do better next time.
我会发挥好一些，因为我不会跟你搭档了。
Well,I will,because I won't be playing with you.
你要知道，有些题目也太难了点。
Hey,some of those are pretty hard.
例如我的冰箱里怎么会有鬼的？
Like,why would there be a ghost in my fridge?
是啊
Yeah.
-那么，星期六晚上。 - 我很愿意。
- So Saturday night? - I'd love to.
太好了。
Great.
你怎么这么长时间才约我？
So how come it took you so long to ask me out?
呃，这听起来有些愚蠢，但是…
Oh,well,this is gonna sound kind of silly..
你还记得我的室友 钱德宾？
but do you remember my roommate,Chandler Bing?
当然，他在你的"乐队"里。
Sure. He was in your "band."
已经16年了，不过那个引号还是挺伤人的。
It's been 16 years,but the air quotes still hurt.
- 对不起。 - 没关系。
- Sorry. - That's okay. Anyway..
呃，总之，我们那时都很喜欢你，
Well,he and I both really liked you a lot..
但是我们又不想为此伤友谊 所以我们约定
but we didn't want it to jeopardize our friendship,so we made a pact..
谁也不能跟你约会。
that neither of us could ask you out.
-真的？ -是啊，怎么了？
- Really? - Yeah,why?
呃，钱德和我曾一块儿亲热。
Well,Chandler and I used to make out.
经常
A lot.
-你们俩？ -对呀
- You did? - Yeah.
-我们常在下课后到实验室去。 -还在我的地盘上？
- We'd go to the science lab after-hours. - And on my turf?!
嘿，那家伙还没来？都一个多小时了。
Hey,where is this guy? It's been over an hour.
他要从泽西赶过来，他说会尽快赶到的。
He's coming from Jersey. He said he'd get here as fast as he could.
哦,对了,菲比的朋友马切 在黄瓜三明治中发现了一只耳环
Oh,by the way,Phoebe's friend Marge found an earring in cucumber sandwich.
呃...它不是我的..
Well,it's not mi..
我今天不在状态
I am not on my game today.
-谁呀？ -警察。
- Who is it? - It's the police.
哦，警察！
The police!
没错，是"好身材"警官。
That's right. It's Officer Goodbody.
出什么事啦，警官？是不是有人调皮了？
What's the matter,officer? Has someone been bad?
丹尼・德・维托（影星）
Danny DeVito
唔，这么多楼梯。
That's a lot of stairs.
唔，老天！
Boy.
你们应该告诉人家这栋楼没电梯。
You should warn people there's no elevator.
我午饭不该吃墨西哥菜。
I should not have had that Mexican food for lunch.
你没事吧，警官…
Are you gonna be okay,Officer..?
-"好身材" -你非要那么说的话。
- Goodbody. - If you say so.
那么，哪位是
So where's the young lady..
我要“逮捕”的年轻女士啊？
who I am supposed to take downtown?
哦，上帝。
Oh,God.
你,亲爱的,被捕了(意同停止)
You,my dear,are under arrest.
心跳停止了?
Cardiac arrest?
好了，谁告诉我插座在哪
All right. Somebody show me where to plug in my box..
我们开始狂欢吧。
and we'll get this party started.
-在这? -对啊!
- Over here? - Yeah.
- 好吧 -瑞秋？
- All right. - Rachel?
-啊？ -呃，你是不是在开我的玩笑？
- Yeah? - Are you kidding?
好吧，我们原来不知道你想要脱衣舞男 所以
We didn't know you wanted a stripper,so we got the phone book..
-我们临时在电话簿上找了一个。 -你们的电话簿有多老了？
- and got the first name we could find. - How old's your phone book?
哦，我的上帝 这个男人要在我的公寓里脱光光！
Oh,my God,this man is gonna get naked in my apartment.
哦，上帝，不要。我可不想看他跳脱衣舞。
God,no. I don't wanna see him take his clothes off.
你们在说我吗？
Are you talking about me?
哦，不。
No.
我是说，我们显然是要看你跳脱衣舞的，
I mean,obviously we wanna see you take your clothes off.
你这个迷人的糖果。
You big piece of eye candy.
好的，女士们，请注意了。
Okay. Okay,ladies,can I have your attention,please?
哦！
Oh,yeah.
有人呼唤法律的长臂了吗？
Did someone call for the long arm of the law?
我要警告你，我有秘密武器呦。
I should warn you,I have a concealed weapon.
我希望你们熟悉本州法律规则。
I hope you're familiar with this state's penal code.
好了好了，玩笑开够了
Okay,okay. Enough teasing.
现在该乐一乐了。
Now for some pleasing.
喔，她躲着我。
She cringed.
这就是我兴奋时候的样子。
This is how I look when I'm turned-on.
你们刚才就是在说我。
You were talking about me before.
我可不需要这些。 我要走了，我的帽子呢？
Look,I don't need this. I'm out of here. Where's my hat?
我干这行已经很长时间了。
Look,I've been in this business for a long time.
骇人听闻。
Shocking.
现在，你付我300块，我这就走人。
Now,if you'll just pay me my $300,I'll be on my way.
- 300？你开什么玩笑？ -没关系，我来拿支票。
- $300? Are you kidding? - That's okay. Let me get my checkbook.
不，你不用付他钱，他什么也没干。
You're not gonna pay him. He didn't do anything.
什么也没干？ 我大老远的从鲍肯搭公交车赶来
Didn't do anything? I took a bus all the way from Hoboken.
我爬了，天知道的，上亿的台阶。
I climbed,I don't know,like,a billion stairs.
这可不像是我一次能干的事。
And it's not like I can take them two at a time.
我不管，我们才不会就为这个付给你300块钱。
I don't care. We're not paying you $300 for this.
那好，你那么保守 欣赏不了男性的身材和魅力
It's not my fault if you're too uptight to appreciate..
这又不是我的错。
the male form in all its glory.
是，我保守，所以我不想看个半大老头儿
Okay,I'm uptight. That's why I don't wanna watch a middle-aged guy..
穿一身我敢说是小孩万圣节的行头跳脱衣舞。
dance around in what I can only assume is a child's Halloween costume.
我也许是从我侄子那儿借的衣服
I may have borrowed this from my nephew..
但我担保衣服里头可是货真价实的真男人。
but let me assure you,what's underneath is all man.
哦，抱歉，你是说真男人还是老男人？
I'm sorry,did you say "all man" or "old man"?
哦，你可真刻薄。
You're mean.
-哦，瞧，警官… -哦，该死，啊！
- Look,officer.. Sir? - Damn it.
没想到吧，大胖子也很脆弱。
Big surprise. The hunk of beef has feelings.
鼓掌。
Applause.
好，亨瑞达 你选了"杰克和吉尔去爬山"。
Okay,Henrietta,you picked "Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill."
我朋友瑞秋有个小孩，我对儿歌很熟悉。
My friend Rachel has a kid. I totally know nursery rhymes.
乔伊，描述以下跟美国国会有关的事物。
Joey,describe these things associated with the United States Congress.
限时20秒。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock,please.
预备，开始。
Ready? Go.
（州议会）
过
Pass.
（圆形大厅）
过
Pass.
（阻挠发言）
过
Pass.
（附录）
-呃，你喉咙后面挂着的小东西。 -悬雍垂(小舌头)。
- The thing hanging in your throat. - Uvula.
哦，那，过。
Then pass.
（联席会议）
好了，亨瑞达，你没有得到所需的点数
Okay. Henrietta,you didn't get all the points you needed..
所以，那就意味着，金 你将进入决胜圈来赢取$10000
so that means,Gene,you are going to the Winner's Circle to try for $10,000.
而且你将与 乔伊崔比亚尼一起参赛。
And you're gonna be going there with Joey Tribbiani.
过
Pass.
不行,你要为别人考虑一下
Nope. You must be thinking of someone else.
我从来没加入过乐队
I was never in a band.
你跟米西.戈尔伯格亲热过？
You made out with Missy Goldberg?
你怎么能在向我保证过之后还这么做？
How could you do that after you promised me?
失陪一下。
Excuse me.
那听起来倒一点不象同性恋。
That didn't make us sound gay at all.
-你违反了君子协定。 -罗斯，那是16年前的事了。
- You broke the pact. - Ross,that was 16 years ago.
那也不行，现在说的是我们之间友谊的基础。
That doesn't matter. We're talking about the foundation of our friendship.
我以为我们之间友谊的基础是难堪的发型。
I believe the foundation of our friendship was unfortunate hair.
要是我们真的算账的话， 你也不是没干过违反君子协定的事。
If we're really gonna do this,it's not like you never broke one of the pacts.
-我没有。 -真的？
- I didn't. - Oh,really?
-没有。 -真的？！
- No. - Oh,really?
-没有。 -安卓.特娜
- No. - Adrienne Turner.
怎么了?
Yes?
-嘿,安卓 -嘿,安卓. 嘿
- Hey,Adrienne. - Hey,Adrienne. Hey.
我从没跟安卓.特娜搅和到一起。
I never did anything with Adrienne Turner.
哦，得了吧，你知道我有多喜欢他。
Oh,please. And you knew how much I liked her.
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know what you're talking about.
真的？还记得那个入学后第一个圣诞节假期
Really? Remember that party freshman year?
前一周的晚会吗？
A week before Christmas vacation? I do.
我记得，当时有人找你。
You had some visitors.
难以置信我们在一个真的大学聚会上。
I can't believe we're at a real college party.
我兴奋的直想尿尿。
I have to pee so bad.
这可真棒。
This is so awesome.
大学男生好可爱。
College guys are so cute.
-嘿，你有男朋友了。 -我知道
- Hey,you've got a boyfriend. - I know.
不过要是有个象克瑞.哈姆那样的想亲我 我是不会拒绝的。
But if a guy who looks like Corey Haim wants to kiss me,I am so gonna let him.
嘿，那是钱德。
Hey,look,there's Chandler.
你知道的，罗斯的傻朋友，说我胖的那个。
That stupid friend of Ross' who said I was fat.
-你要知道，我都瘦掉4磅了。 -就是，一眼就看得出来。
- I've already lost four pounds. - You can so totally tell.
我就知道！
I know!
问问他罗斯在哪。
Well,let's see,maybe he knows where Ross is.
嘿，怎么样？
Hey,how's it going?
-你不是… -对，瑞秋。
- Aren't you..? - Yeah,Rachel.
这是罗斯的妹妹，莫妮卡。 我们感恩节见过。
And this is Ross' sister,Monica. We met at Thanksgiving.
对。那，您怎么样？
Right. So how you doing?
更浪了。
Bitchen.
-嗨，莫妮卡。 -嗨，钱德。
- Hi,Monica. - Hi,Chandler.
我是说，见到你很高兴...才怪。
It's really nice to see you. Not!
好吧。
Okay.
我看看能不能找到罗斯。
I'll see if I can find Ross.
哦我的天，瑞秋，充气椅。
Oh,my God,Rach. Beanbag chairs.
千万别让我坐上去，不然我就起不来了。
Do not let me sit in one of those. We'll be here for days.
听着，安卓，你可不能告诉钱德。
Listen,Adrienne,you can't tell Chandler about this.
哦，相信我，罗斯，我不会告诉任何人的。
Oh,believe me,Ross,I won't be telling anybody about this.
酷。
Cool.
不可能
No way.
我以为你不知道。
I didn't know you knew about that.
但是我知道了，我还很伤心。
Well,I did. And it hurt.
所以我才写了"在休息室被背叛"那首歌。
That's when I wrote the song "Betrayal in the Common Room."
所以那首歌才那么带劲
That's why that song had so much power.
嘿，对不起。
Man,I'm sorry.
好了，那都是陈年往事了。
Look,that was a long time ago.
那，我跟安卓亲热，而你跟米西亲热。
So I made out with Adrienne,and you made out with Missy.
我看我们俩扯平了。
Well,I guess we're even.
我们俩扯平了，对吧？
We are even,right?
还有一件事。 那晚我特生你的气，想报复你
One more thing. I was so pissed at you that night,I wanted to get back at you.
所以我当时想，谁是罗斯最喜欢的人呢。
So I thought,"Who does Ross like more than anybody?"
你对我妈做了什么？
What did you do to my mom?
不是她。
Not her.
我可真醉了。
I am so drunk.
那就怪了，我跟你喝的差不多 怎么我一点事儿没有。
That's weird. I've had the same number of beers as you and don't feel anything.
你们俩玩的好吗？
So you girls having fun?
告诉你吧，蠢货
For your information,ass-munch..
我瘦了4磅，没准儿跳完舞会瘦5磅。
I've lost four pounds. Maybe even five with all the dancing.
-有人定比萨饼了吗？ -哦，是我。
- Somebody order a pizza? - Oh,that's me!
我明天的入学考试算是没戏了。
I am so not gonna do good on my SATs tomorrow.
那，明年也许你可以到我们这儿来上大学 我们可以一块玩玩。
Well,maybe you could go to school here next year and we could totally hang out.
哦，对，是个主意，
Oh,yeah. There's a plan.
那我干脆现在就吃点聪明药丸得了。
Why don't I just start taking my smart pills now.
唔，没准儿你能拿到选美奖学金呢。
Well,maybe you could get in on a beauty scholarship.
哦，别骗人了
What a line.
-那，你都申请了哪些学校？ -唔..
- So where are you applying to? - Well..
你知道，我觉着我要去的地方应该阳光明媚 这很重要
I think it's kind of really important that I go somewhere where there's sun.
所以我想…嗨！
So I'm sort of.. Hey!
我是大学生，还是乐队成员。
I'm in college,and I'm in a band.
那好吧。
Yeah,okay.
怎么啦，你们没见过五十岁的脱衣舞男哭吗？
What's the matter? You never saw a 50-year-old stripper cry before?
你看，算了吧，我们付你钱
You know,it's fine. We'll pay you.
不是那么回事儿，你说的对，我在开谁的玩笑？
No,no,you're right. Who am I kidding?
早几年我就该用那条撑开的护身带上吊算了。
I should have hung up that breakaway jockstrap years ago.
经常的它自己就断开了
Half the time,it just pops off by itself.
也许现在应该是蛋糕和礼物的时间
Maybe now is a good time for cake and presents.
现在我该怎么办？
What am I gonna do? I mean..
我是说，我干这个都32年了。
this has been my life for 32 years.
我只会在人家面前脱衣服。
Taking my clothes off in front of people is all I know.
哦，等等，一定还有别的事你能做的。
No,there's got to be something else that you can do.
我是说，你还有什么技术吗？
I mean,what skills do you have?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我能跳肚皮舞。
I can make my pecs dance.
我可以用屁股蛋儿夹起1美元的钞票。
I can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks.
我能变得毫无廉耻之心。
I can go to that special place inside me where I feel no shame.
那你也许可以从政。
So maybe something in an office.
或者你可以教人跳脱衣舞。
Or you could.. You could teach stripping.
你知道吗？分享你的才能，发扬光大。
You know,share your gift. Pass the torch.
对呀，这主意不赖
You know,actually,that's not a bad idea.
我可以在我的公寓外头干。 我想我妈不会介意的。
I could do it out of my apartment. I don't think my mom would mind.
这下好啦，你感觉好一点了吧？
There you go. Okay. You think you're gonna be okay?
-对，好点了 - 好
- Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah.
世事难料啊。
This is so weird.
你不会知道什么时候曲终人散。
You never know when it's gonna be your last dance.
而且我甚至都没能跳完最后一支舞。
And I didn't even get a chance to finish it.
那你把它跳完吧。
Finish it.
-什么？ -你的最后一次，给我们跳完吧。
- What? - Your last dance. Do it for us.
-当真？ -当真？
- Really? - Really?
是的，他应该最后再做一次他喜爱的事。
Yeah. Yeah,he deserves to do the thing he loves one last time.
好的，准备好了，女士们。
Okay. All right. Get ready,ladies.
好
Okay.
哦，这可真让人兴奋！
Oh,this is so hot!
哦，别，别停下来。
Oh,no,don't stop.
跳不动了。
Have to.
真抱歉你要和我一起干这个
I am so sorry that you have to do this with me.
听着,我知道这个不能送你的孩子去大学..
Listen,I know this won't put your kid through college..
但是,你喜欢《我们的日子》的杯子吗
but would you like a Days of our Lives mug?
我们现在倒数5,4,3,2..
We're back in five,four,three,two..
鼓掌
Applause.
欢迎来到决胜圈。 乔伊，金，你们准备好了吗？
Welcome to the Winner's Circle. Joey,Gene,you guys ready?
- 好了。 - 当然。
- Yeah. - Sure.
好，限时60秒。
Okay. Give me 60 seconds on the clock,please.
预备，开始。
Ready? Go.
（树种）橡树，枫树，榆树，桦树…
Oak. Maple. Elm. Birch.
我-我-我不知道，树种？
I don't know. Types of trees..?
(西班牙语)
Buenos dias. Enchilada. Por favor.
哦，抱歉，我一点不懂西班牙语。
Oh,I'm so sorry,I don't know any Spanish words.
（燃烧物）火柴，蜡烛…
A match. A candle.
扑灭时发出""声的东西。
Things that go: when you put them out.
火炬，篝火…
A torch. A bonfire.
-哦，你的小便。 -燃烧物。
- Your pee. - Things that burn.
（狗会说的话）我要去散散步。 挠挠我的肚皮。
"I'd like to go for a walk." "Scratch my belly."
伙计儿，你是不是跑题了。
Dude. Dude,I think you're losing it.
呃，我有毛，我会吠叫。
"I have fur." "I like to bark."
哦，狗会说话啊
What a dog says.
- 意大利辣香肠… - 比萨饼料。下一个！
- Pepperoni. - Pizza toppings!
（超级名模）辛迪.克劳馥，克莉斯蒂.布林克利 海蒂.克劳姆，克劳迪娅.西佛。
Cindy Crawford. Christie Brinkley. Heidi Klum.
克莉斯蒂.特林顿，凯特.玛斯…
Claudia Schiffer. Christy Turlington. Kate Moss.
钱德永远追不上的姑娘？
Girls Chandler could never get?
- 超级名模！ - 哪儿？！
- Supermodels. - Where?
真没想到你这么生气
I can't believe you're so upset.
-你说呢?你吻了瑞秋
What do you mean? You kissed Rachel.
罗斯,她喝太多了 她第二天甚至什么也不记得了
Ross,she was so drunk she didn't even remember it the next day.
另外我要告诉你,那个并没持续太长
Plus,I should tell you,it did not last long.
嘿!
Hey!
我上大学,而且是乐队成员
I'm in college,and I'm in a band.
啊,好啊!
Yeah,okay.
我已经搞定了一个
And now I've killed one.
嘿，瑞秋在哪？
Hey. Where's Rachel?
她和菲比送脱衣舞男上医院了。
She and Phoebe took the stripper to the hospital.
听起来好象你的"一流茶会"按计划进行
Sounds like your elegant tea party went off just as planned.
你知不知道钱德吻过瑞秋？
Did you know Chandler kissed Rachel?
什么？什么时候？
What? When was this?
上周,我们喝了些酒,然后..
Last week. We had some wine and..
你不知道我是开玩笑的吗
You don't know I'm kidding.
1987年。
1987.
你们俩上学校找我去的那个周末。
The weekend you guys visited me at school.
-我的天，那也太疯狂了。 -是，不过那是很久以前的事了
- Oh,my God. That's wild. - But it was,like,a million years ago.
- 没什么要紧的。 - 但那对我很要紧。
- It doesn't matter. - It matters to me.
- 为什么？ -因为你吻瑞秋的那晚
- Why? - Because the night you kissed Rachel..
是我第一次吻瑞秋。
was the night I kissed Rachel for the very first time.
-你那晚也吻瑞秋了？ - 一晚上两个男人？
- You kissed her that night too? - Two guys in one night?
我还以为她整过鼻子以后才变得放荡了呢。
Oh,I thought she became a slut after she got her nose fixed.
- 说真的，你在哪儿吻的瑞秋？ -是这样的
- Seriously,where did this happen? - Okay..
你告诉我瑞秋在我们屋里睡了之后
after you told me she was passed out in our room..
我进去看看她怎么样了。
I went in there to make sure she was all right.
她躺在我床上，睡在一堆衣服下面。
She was lying on my bed,all buried in people's coats.
呃，我过去想吻她的额头
I went to kiss her on the forehead..
但屋里太暗，我不小心亲到了她的嘴唇
but it was so dark,I accidentally got her lips.
我想回身但我觉得她也开始吻我。
I started to pull away,but then I felt her start to kiss me back.
那只有一瞬间但感觉太奇妙了。
It was only for a second,but it was amazing.
但是现在，我却发现你先吻了她。
And now I find out that you kissed her first.
-呃，等等，你刚才说她在哪张床上？ -我床上。
- Wait,what bed did you say she was on? - Mine.
- 我记得很清楚我把她放到我床上的。 - 不对，她肯定是在我床上。
- I'm sure I put her on my bed. - No,she was definitely on my bed.
我干吗吻完一个姑娘后把她放到你床上？
Why would I kiss a girl and then put her on your bed?
那当时我床上的是谁？
Well,then who was on my bed?
不！不！
No! No!
是的！
Yes!
-你在那堆衣服下面？ -那堆衣服就是我。
- You were under the pile of coats? - I was the pile of coats!
哦，我的上帝！
Oh,my God!
你是我的午夜神秘接吻人？
You were my midnight mystery kisser?!
你是我和瑞秋的初吻？
You were my first kiss with Rachel?!
你就是我这辈子的初吻？！
You were my first kiss ever?!
瞧瞧我结的什么亲家。
What did I marry into?!
哦，倒霉！
Crap!